gearxs.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy Policy

Gearxs.com (“Gearxs”) operates under Gearxs.com. It is Gearxs’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, Gearxs collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Gearxs’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Gearxs’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Gearxs may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Gearxs also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WordPress.com blogs. Gearxs only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to Gearxs’s websites choose to interact with Gearxs in ways that require Gearxs to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Gearxs gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at WordPress.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Gearxs – by purchasing access to the Akismet comment spam prevention service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Gearxs collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Gearxs. Gearxs does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
Gearxs may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Gearxs may monitor the most popular blogs on the WordPress.com site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. Gearxs may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Gearxs does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
Gearxs discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Gearxs’s behalf or to provide services available at Gearxs’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Gearxs’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Gearxs will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Gearxs discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Gearxs believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Gearxs, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Gearxs website and have supplied your email address, Gearxs may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Gearxs and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Gearxs takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Gearxs uses cookies to help Gearxs identify and track visitors, their usage of Gearxs website, and their website access preferences. Gearxs visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Gearxs’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Gearxs’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**  
If Gearxs, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Gearxs goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Gearxs may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Gearxs and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Comments**  
Comments and other content submitted to our Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Gearxs may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Gearxs’s sole discretion. Gearxs encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a WordPress.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
